[EPIC]⚡ You were made to be ruled.
[EPIC]⚡ In the end, it will be every man for himself.
[EPIC]⚡ What do we do?
[EPIC]⚡ We get ready.
[EPIC]⚡ There was an idea to bring together a group of remarkable people,
[EPIC]⚡ so when we needed
[EPIC]⚡ them, they could fight the battles that we never could.
[EPIC]⚡ Gentlemen, what are you prepared to do?
[EPIC]⚡ No offense, but I don't play well with others.
[EPIC]⚡ Big man in a suit of armor.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Take that away.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 What are you?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 A genius billionaire playboy philanthropist.
[EPIC]⚡ If we can't protect the Earth, I'm sure we'll avenge it.
Dr. Banner, your work is unparalleled, and I'm a huge fan of
[DIALOGUE]🗣 the way you lose control
[DIALOGUE]🗣 and turn into an enormous green rage monster.
[EPIC]⚡ Thanks.